cnhi.com 2009-04-20

# Community Newspaper Holdings, Inc. - Community Newspaper Holdings, Inc. (CNHI) - Homepage

## Effective

This Policy was last modified on October 18, 2007.

## Information Practices

Community Newspaper Holdings, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively "Company") understand that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to our web site, (the "Site") and recognize our obligation to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you. We may modify this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") at any time and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent. Please note that the Policy applies only to information collected by Company through the Site, as specified below, and does not govern or apply to any information collected or used by Company through other means.

## Collection of Information

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card number, email addressor other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to make purchases or to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain products or services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP number (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. Because this information helps us in evaluating how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each page of the Site, and the length of visits, we hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation.

## Use of Information

We use your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your orders and administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to personalize the content of the Site to your preferences; to process requests made by you; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that maybe of interest to you; to provide Internet security; where reasonably necessary to enforce our Legal Terms and Conditions of Use; and if there is a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. Company may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other web sites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other web sites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If Company is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information maybe among the transferred assets.

## Privacy of Children

We encourage parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law. Please note that the Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties ("Third Party Sites") which may request Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Company is not responsible for the collection or use of Personal Information collected from any child under the age of 13 at any Third Party Sites. We encourage parents and guardians to review the privacy policies contained on the Third Party Sites. Company disclaims any liability for any third party's use of such Personal Information obtained through using the Third Party Site.

## Your Opportunity to Opt-out of Email Advertising

In the event you do not wish to receive promotional email from us, follow the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive.

## Cookies

When you visit the Site, we or a third party advertiser may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. A "cookie" is a small computer file that is transferred to a computer's hard drive and which permits us to know about site visits. We may use cookies to improve your experience on the Site by making it easier for you to navigate through the Site or to make a site feature work better. Information collected from a "cookie" might include information regarding your browser, type of computer, operating system, Internet service provider and other similar information. Cookie technology may also gather information about the areas you visit on our Site and about the links you may select from within our Site to other areas of the Internet. We use such information in the aggregate to understand which services and resources our visitors prefer and how those services and resources are used. Cookies also allow us to remember you between visits, for example, they may be used for any auto-login feature on the Site or to save any customized preference settings for future visits. We do not extract Personal Information during this process. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features.

## Links

The Site may contain links to Third Party Sites. Company is not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any Third Party Sites. Therefore, Company disclaims any liability for any third party's use of your Personal or Anonymous Information obtained through using the Third Party Site.

## Surveys

From time to time, Company may conduct online surveys through the Site. For example, an opportunity to participate in a survey may be presented in a pop-up window. All surveys are completely voluntary and you may always decline to participate. The information you provide in response to a survey may be shared with our business partners and other third parties, but only in the aggregate, unless we notify you otherwise at the time of collection.

## Public Areas

Company makes some public chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please remember that these areas of the Site are public areas and may be viewed by other visitors to the Site. You should not post any Personal Information in these areas. Any information that is voluntarily disclosed by you in these areas is not proprietary or protected. Please see the section on Submitted Information in the Company's Legal Terms and Conditions of Use for additional information and restrictions regarding these submissions.

## Security

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on our secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. We use Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution.

News from CNHI

Click Here To View Our Local Papers  
  
---  
| 

ALABAMA   
•   [The News Courier, Athens, AL](http://enewscourier.com/)   
•   [The Cullman Times, Cullman, AL](http://cullmantimes.com/)  

Non-daily & other publications located in Alabama:  
•   [Classified Ad Network (CNHI-CAN), Birmingham, AL](http://www.cnhi-can.com/)  
•   [North Jefferson News, Gardendale, AL](http://njeffersonnews.com/)   
•   [The Leeds News, Leeds, AL](http://theleedsnews.net/)  
•   [St. Clair News Aegis, Pell City, AL](http://www.stclairnewsaegis.net/)  

FLORIDA  

Non-daily & other publications located in Florida:  
•   [The Branford News, Branford, FL](http://www.suwanneedemocrat.com/branford)   
•   [The Jasper News, Jasper, FL](http://www.suwanneedemocrat.com/jasper)   
•   [Suwannee Democrat, Live Oak, FL](http://suwanneedemocrat.com/)   
•   [The Mayo Free Press, Mayo, FL](http://suwanneedemocrat.com/mayo)   

GEORGIA   
•   [Americus Times Recorder, Americus, GA ](http://americustimesrecorder.com/)   
•   [Cordele Dispatch, Cordele, GA ](http://cordeledispatch.com/)   
•   [The Daily Citizen, Dalton, GA ](http://daltondailycitizen.com/)   
•   [The Union-Recorder, Milledgeville, GA ](http://unionrecorder.com/)   
•   [The Moultrie Observer, Moultrie, GA ](http://moultrieobserver.com/)   
•   [Thomasville Times-Enterprise, Thomasville, GA ](http://timesenterprise.com/)   
•   [The Tifton Gazette, Tifton, GA ](http://tiftongazette.com/)   
•   [Valdosta Daily Times, Valdosta, GA ](http://valdostadailytimes.com/)

Non-daily & other publications located in Georgia: 

IOWA   
•   [Ad Express & Daily Iowegian, Centerville, IA ](http://dailyiowegian.com/)   
•   [Clinton Herald, Clinton, IA ](http://clintonherald.com/)   
•   [The Oskaloosa Herald, Oskaloosa, IA ](http://oskaloosaherald.com/)   
•   [Ottumwa Daily Courier, Ottumwa, IA ](http://ottumwacourier.com/)

Non-daily publications located in Iowa:  
•   [Knoxville Journal Express, Knoxville, IA](http://www.journalexpress.net/)   
•   [Pella Chronicle, Pella, IA](http://www.pellachronicle.com/)   

ILLINOIS   
•   [Commercial News, Danville, IL ](http://commercial-news.com/)   
•   [Effingham Daily News, Effingham, IL ](http://effinghamdailynews.com/)   
•   [Mt. Vernon Register News, Mt. Vernon, IL ](http://register-news.com/)   
•   [Shelbyville Daily Union, Shelbyville, IL ](http://shelbyvilledailyunion.com/)

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Times-Leader, McLeansboro, IL](http://mcleansborotimesleader.com/)   

INDIANA   
•   [The Herald Bulletin, Anderson, IN](http://heraldbulletin.com/)   
•   [Goshen News, Goshen, IN](http://goshennews.com/)   
•   [Greensburg Daily News, Greensburg, IN ](http://greensburgdailynews.com/)   
•   [The Evening News, Jeffersonville, IN ](http://news-tribune.net/)   
•   [Kokomo Tribune, Kokomo, IN ](http://kokomotribune.com/)   
•   [The Lebanon Reporter, Lebanon, IN ](http://reporter.net/)   
•   [The Pharos-Tribune, Logansport, IN ](http://pharostribune.com/)   
•   [The Tribune, New Albany, IN ](http://news-tribune.net/)   
•   [Rushville Republican, Rushville, IN ](http://rushvillerepublican.com/)   
•   [The Tribune Star, Terre Haute, IN ](http://tribstar.com/)   
•   [Washington Times Herald, Washington, IN ](http://washtimesherald.com/)   

Non-daily publications and other businesses in Indiana:  
•   [Hendricks County Flyer, Avon, IN](http://flyergroup.com/)   
•   [XL Marketing, Carmel, IN](http://www.xl-marketing.com/)   
•   [Batesville Herald-Tribune, Batesville, IN](http://batesvilleheraldtribune.com/)   
•   [The Zionsville Times Sentinel, Zionsville, IN](http://timessentinel.com/)   

KANSAS   

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Farm Talk, Parsons, KS](http://farmtalknewspaper.com/)   

| 

KENTUCKY   
•   [The Independent, Ashland, KY ](http://dailyindependent.com/)   
•   [Times Tribune, Corbin, KY ](http://thetimestribune.com/)   
•   [Glasgow Daily Times, Glasgow, KY ](http://glasgowdailytimes.com/)   
•   [Richmond Register, Richmond, KY ](http://richmondregister.com/)   
•   [Commonwealth Journal, Somerset, KY ](http://somerset-kentucky.com/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   Greenup News-Times, Greenup, KY  
•   [Grayson Journal Enquirer, Grayson, KY](http://journal-times.com/)   
•   [The Sentinel Echo, London, KY](http://sentinel-echo.com/)   
•   [Wayne County Outlook, Monticello, KY](http://wcoutlook.com/)   
•   [Morehead News, Morehead, KY](http://www.themoreheadnews.com/)   
•   [Olive Hill Times, Olive Hill, KY](http://journal-times.com/)   
•   [McCreary County Record, Whitley City, KY](http://mccrearyrecord.com/)   

MASSACHUSETTS   
•   [Gloucester Daily Times, Gloucester, MA ](http://gloucestertimes.com/)   
•   [The Daily News of Newburyport, Newburyport, MA ](http://newburyportnews.com/)   
•   [The Eagle-Tribune, North Andover, MA ](http://eagletribune.com/)   
•   [The Salem News, Salem, MA](http://salemnews.com/)   

Non-daily publications in Massachusetts:  
•   [Andover Townsman, Andover, MA](http://andovertownsman.com/)   
•   [The Haverhill Gazette, Haverhill, MA](http://hgazette.com/)   

MARYLAND   
•   [Cumberland Times News, Cumberland, MD ](http://times-news.com/)   

Non-daily publications in Maryland:  

MICHIGAN   
•   [The Record-Eagle, Traverse City, MI](http://www.record-eagle.com/)  
•   [Grand Traverse Herald, Traverse City, MI](http://www.record-eagle.com/herald.htm)  

MINNESOTA   
•   [Mankato Free Press, Mankato, MN ](http://mankatofreepress.com/)   

Non-daily publications in Minnesota:  
•   [Home Magazine, Mankato, MN](http://homemagonline.com/)   
•   [The Land, Mankato, MN](http://thelandonline.com/)  

MISSOURI   
•   [The Joplin Globe, Joplin, MO ](http://joplinglobe.com/)   

MISSISSIPPI   
•   [Laurel Leader-Call, Laurel, MS ](http://leadercall.com/)   
•   [The Meridian Star, Meridian, MS ](http://meridianstar.com/)   
•   [Picayune Item, Picayune, MS ](http://picayuneitem.com/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   [The Star Herald, Koscuisko, MS](http://starherald.net/)   
•   [The Newton Record, Newton, MS](http://thenewtonrecord.com/)   
•   The Poplarville Democrat, Poplarville, MS  

NORTH CAROLINA   
•   [The Daily Southerner, Tarboro, NC ](http://dailysoutherner.com/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Stanly News & Press, Albemarle, NC](http://thesnaponline.com/)  
•   [The Randolph Guide, Asheboro, NC](http://randolphguide.com/)  

NEW HAMPSHIRE   
Non-daily publications:  
•   [Derry News / Weekender, Derry, NH ](http://derrynews.com/)   

NEW YORK   
•   [Lockport Union-Sun & Journal, Lockport, NY ](http://lockportjournal.com/)   
•   [The Journal-Register, Medina, NY ](http://journal-register.com/)   
•   [Niagara Gazette, Niagara Falls, NY ](http://niagara-gazette.com/)   
•   [Tonawanda News, North Tonawanda, NY ](http://tonawanda-news.com/)   
•   [The Daily Star, Oneonta, NY](http://www.thedailystar.com/)  
•   [The Press-Republican, Plattsburgh, NY](http://www.pressrepublican.com/)

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Cooperstown Crier, Cooperstown, NY](http://www.coopercrier.com/)

| 

OHIO   
•   [The Star Beacon, Ashtabula, OH ](http://starbeacon.com/)   

OKLAHOMA   
•   [The Ada Evening News, Ada, OK ](http://adaeveningnews.com/)   
•   [Chickasha Express Star, Chickasha, OK ](http://chickashanews.com/)   
•   [Claremore Daily Progress, Claremore, OK ](http://claremoreprogress.com/)   
•   [The Duncan Banner, Duncan, OK ](http://duncanbanner.com/)   
•   [Edmond Sun, Edmond, OK ](http://edmondsun.com/)   
•   [Enid News & Eagle, Enid, OK ](http://enidnews.com/)   
•   [McAlester News-Capital, McAlester, OK ](http://mcalesternews.com/)   
•   [The Muskogee Phoenix, Muskogee, OK ](http://muskogeephoenix.com/)   
•   [The Norman Transcript, Norman, OK ](http://normantranscript.com/)   
•   [Pauls Valley Daily Democrat, Pauls Valley, OK](http://paulsvalleydailydemocrat.com/)   
•   [Pryor Daily Times, Pryor, OK ](http://pryordailytimes.com/)   
•   [The Stillwater Newspress, Stillwater, OK ](http://stwnewspress.com/)   
•   [Tahlequah Daily Press, Tahlequah, OK ](http://tahlequahdailypress.com/)   
•   [Woodward News, Woodward, OK](http://woodwardnews.net/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   Ft. Gibson Times, Ft. Gibson, OK  
•   Hartshorne Sun, Hartshorne, OK   
•   [The Midwest City Sun, Midwest City, OK](http://mwcsun.com/)   
•   [The American, Moore, OK](http://themooreamerican.com/)   
•   [Tuttle Times, Tuttle, OK](http://tuttletimes.com/)   
•   Stilwell Democrat Journal, Stilwell, OK  
•   [Waurika News Democrat, Waurika, OK](http://waurikademocrat.com/)  
•   Westville Reporter, Westville, OK  

PENNSYLVANIA   
•   [The Tribune-Democrat, Johnstown, PA ](http://tribune-democrat.com/)   
•   [The Meadville Tribune, Meadville, PA ](http://meadvilletribune.com/)   
•   [New Castle News, New Castle, PA ](http://ncnewsonline.com/)   
•   [The Herald, Sharon, PA ](http://sharonherald.com/)   
•   [The Daily Item, Sunbury, PA](http://www.dailyitem.com/)  
•   [The Danville News, Danville, PA](http://www.dailyitem.com/0700_the_danville_news)

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Allied News, Grove City, PA](http://alliednews.com/)   

TENNESSEE   
Non-daily publications:  
•   [Crossville Chronicle, Crossville, TN](http://crossville-chronicle.com/)   

TEXAS   
•   [Athens Daily Review, Athens, TX ](http://athensreview.com/)   
•   [Cleburne Times Review, Cleburne, TX ](http://cleburnetimesreview.com/)   
•   [Corsicana Daily Sun, Corsicana, TX ](http://corsicanadailysun.com/)   
•   [Gainesville Daily Register, Gainesville, TX ](http://gainesvilleregister.com/)   
•   [Greenville Herald Banner, Greenville, TX ](http://heraldbanner.com/)   
•   [The Huntsville Item, Huntsville, TX ](http://itemonline.com/)   
•   [Jacksonville Daily Progress, Jacksonville, TX ](http://jacksonvilleprogress.com/)   
•   [Mineral Wells Index, Mineral Wells, TX ](http://mineralwellsindex.com/)   
•   [The Orange Leader, Orange, TX ](http://orangeleader.com/)   
•   [Palestine Herald-Press, Palestine, TX ](http://palestineherald.com/)   
•   [The Port Arthur News, Port Arthur, TX ](http://www.panews.com/)   
•   [San Marcos Daily Record, San Marcos, TX ](http://sanmarcosrecord.com/)   
•   [Weatherford Democrat, Weatherford, TX ](http://weatherforddemocrat.com/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Rockwall County Herald Banner, Greenville, TX](http://rockwallheraldbanner.com/)   
•   [Royse City Herald Banner, Greenville, TX](http://www.roysecityheraldbanner.com/)   
•   [Commerce Journal, Commerce, TX](http://commercejournal.com/)   
•   [Cedar Creek Pilot, Gun Barrel City, TX](http://cedarcreekpilot.com/)   

WEST VIRGINIA   
•   [The Register Herald, Beckley, WV ](http://register-herald.com/)   
•   [Bluefield Daily Telegraph, Bluefield, WV ](http://bdtonline.com/)   
•   [Times West Virginian, Fairmont, WV ](http://timeswv.com/)   

Non-daily publications:  
•   [Montgomery Herald, Montgomery, WV](http://montgomery-herald.com/)   
•   [The Fayette Tribune, Oak Hill, WV](http://fayettetribune.com/)   
•   Princeton Times, Princeton, WV  

---|---|---
